Guide to Peter P. Carr Papers RG.055
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series I: American Options, 1965-2002; 60 Linear Feet
  - Myneni, Ravi; The Optimal Exercise Boundary and the American Equity Put, 1989-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Myneni, Ravi; The Pricing of the American Option, Stanford Working Paper, 1990-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Noubir, M.; "Pricing American and Bermudan Interest Rate Options in the Market Models," Credit Lyonnais-Risk Conferences, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Omberg, Edward; The Valuation of American Put Options with Exponential Exercise Policies, Advances in Futures and Options Research, 1987; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Omberg, Arbitraging Options: The Case of the Live Real Option and Dead Synthetic Option, 1989-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Parkinson, Michael JB; Option Pricing: The American Put, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Rogers, L.C.G.; Monte Carlo Valuation of American Options, University of Bath, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Samuelson/McKean, Rational Theory of Warrant Pricing Appendix: A Free Boundary Problem for the Heat Equation Arising from a Problem in Mathematical Economics, Industrial Management Review, 1965; 60 Linear Feet (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Reddy, Verification of American Put, 1990-08-2000-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Salminen, Paavo; Optimal Stopping and American Put Options, Theory of Stochastic Processes, 1995; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Schroder, Mark; A Reduction Method Applicable to Compound Option Formulas, Management Science, 1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Schroder, M.; Computing Parity Results for American Options Using a Change of Measure, SUNY Buffalo Working Paper, 1996-05; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Stapleton/Subrahmanyam, "The Valuation of American Options in Stochastic Interest Rate Economies", 1991-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Stensland and Tjostheim, Optimal Investments Using Empirical Dynamic Programming with Application to Natural Resources, 1989-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Stentoft, L.; Assessing the Least Squares Monte-Carlo Approach to American Option Valuation, 2001-08; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Stentoft, L.; Convergence of the Least Squares Monte-Carlo Approach to American Option Valuation, 2002-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Stentoft, Lars; Pricing American Options when the Underlying Stock Price Exhibits Time-Varying Volatility, 2002-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Su, Yi: University of Maryland at Risk Conferences; "Pricing American Options via Simulation: A Comparison of Monte Carlo Simulation Approaches", Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Subrahmanyam, M.G. & Yu, G.G.; Pricing and Hedging American Options: A Unified Method and its Efficient Implementation, Working Paper, 1993-09 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Taylor, Howard; Management Science, September '67; Evaluating a Call Option and Optimal Timing Strategy in the Stock Market, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Tilley, J.; Morgan Stanley Working Paper; Valuing American Options in a Path Simulation Model, 1992-05-15 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Tsitsiklis & Van Roy, Optimal Stopping of Markov Processes: Hilbert Space Theory, Approximation Algorithms, & an Application to Pricing High-Dimensional Financial Derivatives, 1998-10 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Tsitsiklis & Van Roy, Regression Methods for Pricing Complex American-Style Options, 2000-08 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Touzi, N.; Applied Mathematics and Optimization, '99, American Options Exercise Boundary when the Volatility Changes Randomly, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Van Moerbeke, Pierre; On Optimal Stopping and Free Boundary Problems, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Villeneuve, Stephane; Exercise Regions of American Options on Several Assets, 1997-06 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Viswanathan, Ravi; American Option's Bounds: Tanaka's Formula and Snell Envelopes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Wei, Jason Z.; Valuing American Equity Options with a Stochastic Interest Rate: A Note, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Wu, L., Kwok, Y., Zhu, Y.; Fixed-Domain Finite Difference Methods for American Options, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Wu & Kwok, A Front-Fixing Finite Difference Method for the Valuation of American Options, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Yaksick, R.; Expected Optimal Exercise Time of a Perpetual American Option: A Closed-Form Solution, Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Yang & Yuan, Another New Way to Price American Options by Using the Interior Point Method, 1999-08-05 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Yu, Gang; Valuation of American Options in Stochastic Interest Rate Economics, 1992-03 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Yu, Gang George; Essays on the Valuation of American Options, 1993-04 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Yu, Gang; Valuation of American Options: A Simplified Approach and Applications, 1992-12 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - A Simplified Approach to the Valuation of American Options and Applications, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Yu, Kwok & Wu; Valuation of American Lookback Options, 1997-10 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Zhang, Xiao; Numerical Analysis of American Option Pricing in a Jump-Diffusion Model, Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Bates, David; The Crash of '87, Relative Prices of OTM Calls & Puts under Standard Distributional Hypotheses, Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - T. Gayley, A Mathlink Program for Accessing Binary Files, Mathematica Journal, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - A. Conze, European Path Dependent Options: The Case of Geometric Averages, 1989-09 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - M. Curran, Valuing Asian and Portfolio Options by Conditioning on the Geometric Mean Price, 1993-05 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - D. Grant, G. Vora & D. Weeks; Path-Dependent Options: Extending the Monte Carlo Simulation Approach, 1993-11 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - J. M. Haykov, A Better Control Variate for Pricing Standard Asian Options, Journal of Financial Engineering 2, 207-216, 1993-09 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - J. Hull, Interest Rate Exotics, Risk Exotic Options Conference, 1994-04 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - F. Jamshidian, Hedging Quantos, Differential Swaps and Ratios, 1993-05 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - E. Reiner, Quanto Mechanics, Risk, Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - M. Rubenstein, Two Into One, Risk 4, #5, 1991-05 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - M. York, On Some Exponential Functionals of Browian Motion, Advances in Applied Probability 24, 509-531, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - P.P. Boyle & S.H. Lau, Bumping Up Against the Barrier with the Binomial Method, 1994; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - G.L. Gastineau, An Introduction to Special-Purpose Derivatives: Roll Up Puts, Roll Down...J. Derivatives, 1994; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - C.B. Huynh, Back to Baskets, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - H.M. Kat, Contingent Premium Options, 1994; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - S.H. Babbs, Binomial Valuation of Lookback Options, 1992-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - C.A. Ball, W.N. Torous & A.E. Tschoegl; On Inferring Standard Deviations from Path Dependent Options, Economics Letters 18, 1985-01-15; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - D. Beaglehole; Down and Out, Up and In Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - R. Benson & N. Daniel; Up, Over and Out; Risk 4 No. 6, 1991-06; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Y.Z. Bergman, Pricing Path Contingent Claims, Research In Finance 5, 1985; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - M. Hudson, The Value in Going Out, Risk, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - F. Jamshidian, Hedging and Evaluating Differential Swaps, 1993-04; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Reiner, Valuation of Average-Dependent Options, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - D.R. Rich, The Mathematical Foundations of Barrier Option Pricing Theory, Advances in Futures and Options Research, Forthcoming, 1994-01; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - D.R. Rich & D.M. Chance, An Alternative Approach to the Pricing of Options on Multiple Assets, Journal of Financial Engineering 2, 1993; 60 Linear Feet (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - M. Rubinstein & E. Reiner, Breaking Down the Barriers, Risk 4, No. 8, 1991-09 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - J. Wei, Streams of Consequence, Risk 7, #1, 1994-01 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - J.Z. Wei, Valuing Differential Swaps, 1993-01-08 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - K.I. Amin, Jump Diffusion Option Valuation in Discrete Time, Journal of Finance Vol. XLVIII, #5, 1993-12 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - G. Barone-Adesi & R.E. Whaley, Efficient Analytic Approximation of American Option Values, Journal of Finance Vol. XLII, 1987-06 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - R. Breen, The Accelerated Binomial Option Pricing Model, Journal of Financial and Quantitative Analysis 26, #2, 1991-06 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - A. Carverhill & N. Webber, American Options: Theory and Numerical Analysis, 1988-07 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - M. Chesney, Pricing American Currency Options: An Analytical Approach, Centre HEC ISA, France, Undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - N.J. Cutland & E. Kopp, From Discrete to Continuous Financial Models: New Convergence Results for Option Pricing, Mathematical Finance 3, #2, 101-123, 1993-04 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - R. Geske & H.E. Johnson, The American Put Option Valued Analytically, Journal of Finance Vol. XXXIX, #5, 1984-12 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - L.W. MacMillan, Analytic Approximation for the American Put Option, Advances in Futures and Options Research. Vol. 1, Part A, 119-139, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - R.C. Merton, M.J. Brennan & E.S. Schwartz, The Valuation of American Put Options, Journal of Finance Vol. XXXII, #2, 1977-05 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - E. Omberg, The Valuation of American Put Options with Exponential Exercise Policies, Advances in Futures and Options Research Vol 2: 117-142, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - M.G. Subrahmanyam & G.G. Yu, Pricing and Hedging American Options: A Unified Method and its Efficient Implementation, 1993-09 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - The Economics of the Reflection Principle and Girsanov's Theorem, Undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - EPCS - European Put Call Symmetry, 1993-12-1994-05 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Even Functions, Undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - APCS Resubmit, 1996-11-1997-06 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Letter from Bjerksund & Stensland, 1998-11-04 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Olsen & Stensland, Invariant Controls in Stochastic Allocation Problems, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Bjerksund & Stensland, American Exchange Options and a Put-Call Transformation: A Note, Journal of Business Finance and Accounting, 1993-09 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Bjerksund & Stensland, Closed-Form Approximation of American Options, Scandinavian Journal of Management, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Continuous Random Variable and Notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - AMEX Letter, 1993-09-22-1993-12-16 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - American Put-Cdn Call Symmetry, Undated (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Margrabe's Web Site, 1999-08-03 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - APC Pres, Undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - APCS in Same Economy, Undated (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Barrier Option Typeups, Undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Chesney Rewrite, Undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Green's Function & PCS, Undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Hedging ITM UIC's with using PCS UIP's, Undated (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - FX Options, Undated (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Installment Options, 1993-08-1993-10 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Installment Stoptions (on Spot), Undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Installment Options, 1993-08-03 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - (Installment) (St)options on Forward, Undated (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Journal Submission, 1995-07-26-1997-05-13 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Linear Homogeneity, Undated (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Lookbacks, Undated (Box 3, Folder 95)
- Series II: APCS & AMOL, 1989-1998
  - Manuscript, 1993-06-1996-11-13 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Passthru Options, Undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Perpetual Options Counterexample, Undated (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Physical Interpretation of Put Call Symmetry, Undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Portfolio Ins / Zero Cost Collars, Undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Put Call Equivalence, Undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - PCEE, 1994-05-20-1995-12-13 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Put Call Symmetry for American Options, 1994-03 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Put Call Symmetry for European Options, 1996-09 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Proofs for EPCS, Undated (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Put Writing Strategy, 1992-08-20 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Stochastic Vol. Papers, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Stoptions, Undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Terminology & Notation, Undated (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Bergman, Grundy & Wiener; General Properties of Option Prices, 1996-01 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Li, Ritchken, Sankarasubramanian; Lattice Models for Pricing American Interest Rate Claims, 1993-11 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Rubinstein, M.; As Simple as One, Two, Three; Risk 8, #1, 1995-01 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Practical Issues in Using Interest Rate Models, Iris Financial Engineering & Systems, Inc., Undated (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Analytic Approxn. of Amer. Put Options (AAA), Undated (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Analytic Formulas for Barrier Options, Undated (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Crank Nicholson, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Dewynne & Wilmott, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Douglas Equations, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Duanmu Conversations, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Early Exercise Premium, 1994-05 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Financial Interpretations, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Funding, 1994-01 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Implied Vol. Fin. from America, 1990-08 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Interpolation, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Method of Lines, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Ode's Lit., Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Parabolic PDE's Literature, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - PDE's, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Richardson Extrapolation, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Remberg Integration, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Selling Code, 1993-01-06-1994-05-12 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Similarity Solutions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Space Discretization, Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Spreadsheet - AMOL, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - State & Time Dependent Parameters, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Step Size, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Strikwerda, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Term Structure, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Two Free Boundaries, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Unequal Time Steps, Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Getting Results for Caution Options, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Nguyen D., On a Free Boundary Problem for the Heat Equation, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Duffie & Glynn, Stanford University Working Paper, Estimation of Continuous-Time Markov Processes Sampled at Random Time Intervals, 1996-03-14 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Call Spread, Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - CEV, Undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Clipped Put, Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Conferences, 1994-01-31-1996-01-08 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Cons'n & Portfolio Strategies, Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Convertible Bond, Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Delayed Exercise Premium, Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Diagonalizing Transformation, Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - European Put Closed Form, 1994-05 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Exponential Fixup, Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Extensions/To Do, Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Faguet, Dimitri, 1993-07-08-1995-02-27 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Frolov, Dimitri 257-4925, Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Futures Options, Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Gear, Undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - General BC's, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Geske & Johnson, Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Hedging with Options, Undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Hedging Random Maturity Claims with Dynamic Trading in 3 Long-Lined Securities, Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - High Order CDE & European-Style Claims, 1995-02 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - HP12C, Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Implying Volatility, Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Interest Rate Models, Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Interpolation, Undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - "Willed" Puts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Linear Coeff's & Confluent Hypergeom's, 1995-08 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Valuing Corp. Debt with AMOL, Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Widder, D.; Nov. '82; The Inversion of a Transform Related to the Laplace Transform and to Heat Conduction, 1998-05-14 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Series III: Basket Options, 1993-2005
  - Zou, J.; A New Metric for Valuing and Ranking Equity Options: Strike-Adjusted Spread - Applications to Basket Options, Undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Zhang, P.; Chapter 27 of book, Basket Options, Undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Wilmott, P.; Ch. 11.4 in "Derivatives," Options on Many Underlyings, Undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Ware & Lari-Lavassani, Algorithms for Portfolio Options, 2000-09-13 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Wan, Henry; Pricing American-style Basket Options by Implied Binomial Tree, 2002-03 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Valdez & Dhaene, Bounds for Sums of Non-Independent Log-Elliptical Random Variables, 2003-05-25 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Nelken, I.; Ch. in "Pricing, Hedging & Trading Exotic Options" called Basket Options, Undated (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Naus, J.I.; The Distribution of the Logarithm of the Sum of Two Log-normal Variates, Undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Li & Zhang, ML Working Paper '97, Hurdles Removed, 1996-10-17 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Laurence & Wang, Sharp Distribution Free Bounds and Optimal Hedge Ratios for Basket Options, 2003-08-13 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Janson & Tysk, Properties of Options on Several Underlying Assets: Extended Summary, 2001-11-30 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Huynh, C. B.; Back to Baskets, Risk '98, Undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Bhansali, R.; Baskets and the Edgeworth Expansion, Undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Laurence & Wang, Sharp Upper and Lower Bounds for Basket Options, 2003-09-09 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Laurence & Wang, Valuing and Hedging Basket Options without Distributional Assumptions, 2003-06-01 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Lee, Wang & Karim; Index Volatility Surface via Moment-Matching Techniques, 2003-12 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Mitchell, R.; Permanence of the Log-Normal Distribution, Journal of the Optical Society of America 58 (1988)1267, 1999-05-14 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Musiela & Rutkowski, "Basket Options" in Martingale Methods in Financial Modelling, Undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Ouertani, N.; Basket Options on Heterogenous Underlying Assets, 2003-04 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Ravindran, K.; "The Basket Option Contract" chapter in Customized Derivatives, Undated (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Romeo, Da Costa & Bardou; Broad Distribution Effects in Sums of Lognormal Random Variables, 2002-11-14 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Safak, Aysel; Statistical Analysis of the Power Sum of Multiple Correlated Log-Normal Components, IEEE Transactions, 2003-02 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Schwartz & Yeh, On the Distribution Function and Moments of Power Sums with Log-Normal Components, Bell System Technical Journal, Undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Laurence & Wang, Valuing and Hedging Basket Options without Distributional Assumptions, 2003-06-07 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Laurence & Stredulinsky, A Comparison Principle for an American Option on Several Assets: Index and Spread Options, 2000-11 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Lamberton & Lapeyre, Hedging Index Options with Few Assets, Mathematical Finance, 1993-01 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Hat, H.; Ch. 4: Index-Linked Cash Flows, Undated (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Ju, N.; Pricing Asian and Basket Options via Taylor Expansion of the Underlying Volatility, 2000-09-14 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Jonasz, Miroslaw & Fournie, George; Correction to 41(1996)774 (Jun 96), Limnology & Oceanography (1996)1814, Undated (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Jonasz & Fournier, Approximation of the Size Distribution of Marine Particles by a Sum of Log-Normal Functions, Limnol. Oceanogr., 1996 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Hobson, Laurence & Wang, Static-Arbitrage Upper Bounds for the Prices of Basket Options, 2004-06-03-2005-02-18 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Hamdan, M. A.; The Logarithm of the Sum of Two Correlated Log-Normal Variates, Journal of the American Statistical Association, 1971-03 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Grannis, Scott; An Idea Whose Time Has Come, Risk Magazine, Undated (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Gentle, David; Basket Weaving, Risk, 1993-06 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Fenton, L.; The Sum of Log-Normal Probability Distributions in Scatter Transmission Systems, IRE Transactions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Falloon, W.; Basket Cases, Risk Magazine, 1998-03 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Deelstra, Liinev & Van Maele; Applied Probability Trust, 2002-11-15 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Dahl & Benth, Valuation of Asian Basket Options with Quasi-Monte Carlo Techniques and Singular Value Decomposition, 2001-01 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Curran, M.; Valuing Asian and Portfolio Options by Conditioning on the Geometric Mean Price, Kidder, 1993-05-02 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - d'Aspremont, A.; A Harmonic Analysis Solution to the Static Basket Arbitrage Problem, 2003-09-02 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Castellacci & Siclari, A Framework for Valuing Exotic Asian and Basket Options, 2001-10-10 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Beaulieu, Abu-Dayya & McLane; Estimating the Distribution of a Sum of Independent Lognormal Random Variables, IEEE Transactions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Bos & Ware, Solving Multi-Asset Black-Scholes with Time Dependent Volatility, 2000-02-11 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Barakat, R.; Sums of Independent Lognormally Distributed Random Variables, Journal of the Optical Society of America, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Ashraff, Tarczan & Wu; Safe Crossing, Risk, 1995-07 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Basket Option, Mtgs/Email at Morgan Stanley, 1998-06-26-1998-09-29 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Brigo, Mercurio, Rapisarda & Scotti; Approximated Moment-Matching Dynamics for Basket-Options Simulation, 2002-10-23 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Avellaneda, Boyer-Olson, Busca & Friz; Reconstructing Volatility, Risk, 2002-10 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Using Bessel Squared Process, Undated (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Imagine Guide Discussion of Basket Securities, Undated (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Book Discussions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Sum of 2 Lognormals, 2000-12-15 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Book of American FX Basket Options, 1999-08-28 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Basket Options in EFP, 1999-03-09 (Box 4, Folder 110)
- Series IV: Binomial Local Time (BLT), 1988-1991
  - Finite Calculus, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - BLT Root, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - BLT Presentation, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Journal of Finance Submission, 1990-12-27-1991-02-27 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Journal of Financial and Quantitative Analysis Submission, 1991-03-29 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Charges to Add, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Literature Review, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - BLT Press, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lates version of "European Option Valuation when Carrying Costs are Unknown", 1989-1990; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Journal of Financial and Quantitative Analysis Submission: "European Option valuation When Carrying Costs are Unknown", 1990-1991; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - EOV Presentation, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - WFA Conference Submission, 1989-11-20; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - EOV Comments, 1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Derivations, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Equivalence, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Extensions, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - TEX, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Computer Searches, 1988-1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - EOV Originals, 1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - EOV Print, 1989; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Editorial Changes, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Binomial Convergence, Undated; 60 Linear Feet (Box 5, Folder 22)